Minh Nguyen

Marketing Coordinator / Graphic+Web Designer

Phone: (512) 825 9661

Email: MinhStudios@gmail.com
Portfolio: www.Minhstudios.com
Linkedin.com/in/minhstudios

Summary

Minh Nguyen is a graphic designer with 8 years professional experience with a focus in print, illustration, logo and web design. He also has experience with Wordpress, Bootstrap, photography, drawing, and painting. Minh aims to have a continued advancement in web development as part of his goal set. Born in Vietnam and raised in Austin (Texas), he attended Texas State University, gaining his Bachelors of Fine Arts in (2010). After completing an internship in San Antonio (Clockwork Studios), Minh began working in-house for a Real Estate firm where he was immersed in website design, real estate photography, print, and direct mail. He soon became a marketing coordinator for Newmark Knight Frank and works with reputable clients to market their commercial real estate assets. He is responsible for the day-to-day production of proposals, offering memorandums, marketing collateral, flyers, marketing videos, and research reports. With a passion to always grow and become a better designer, he is open and available for any multi-faceted project needs.

Experience

MARKETING COORDINATOR | DEC 2017 - SEPT 2020 Newmark Knight Frank, Austin, TX

- » Marketed over +\$1 billion in multifamily in real estate transactions
- » Create proposals & offer memorandums for multi-million dollar properties
- » Market overview research and coordination of team to client projects

GRAPHIC DESIGNER (CONTRACTOR) | NOV 2017 - May 2018 Texas Hospital Association, Austin, TX

» Producing White Pages, layouts, editing, logos, and other print materials

GRAPHIC+WEB DESIGNER / PHOTOGRAPHER | NOV 2014 - NOV 2017 The Carvajal Group, Austin, TX

- » Design fliers, brochures, banners, direct mail, logos and print materials
- » Creating and maintain Wordpress website periodically for listings
- » Real estate photography and post-editing for listings
- » Create MLS signs, billboard graphics, and magazine ads

INTERN GRAPHIC DESIGNER | JAN 2012 - MAY 2012 Clockwork Studios, San Antonio, TX

- » Edits to client projects and finalization
- » Creating solution to client projects with brainstorming
- » Logo and campaign branding creation

Education

WEB DESIGN | 2016 - 2017

Austin Community College & Udemy.com | Austin, TX (Post bachelors education)

COMMUNICATION DESIGN | 2006 - 2010

Bachelors of Fine Arts | Texas State University | San Marcos, TX Cum Laude Achievement | GPA: 3.7/4.0

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- » Dean's List 2010
- » Dean's List 2009
- » High achievements in Printmaking
- » High achievements in Sculpture & Drawing

Skillset / Abilities

Design Softwares: Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Dreamweaver, Flash, and Premiere

Web-based Application: HTML/CSS, FTP Client and Wordpress

Hand skills: Drawing, Painting, and Printmaking

Office Application: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Office 365, Mac, Windows, and Excel

Photography: Real Estate Photography and Lightroom CC post editing

Campaign E-blast Interface: Listing Lab

References

Shawn Meeks

Design Professor at Fort Lewis College (Durango, Co) 210.382.9091 | scmeek@fortlewis.edu

Erik Le

Operational Manager at Leadspace (Austin, Tx) 512.998.3944 | erik.le1082@gmail.com

Angela Clapper

Facilities Coordinator II at HID Global (Austin, Tx) 512.627.1000 | angela.clapper@hidglobal.com

Jose Luis Salazar

UX Developer at Community Impact Newspaper (Austin, Tx) 512.940.8604 | choche_@hotmail.com